speedycash.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Speedy Cash

## What does Speedy Cash do with your personal information?

#### What?

We collect information from a variety of sources, including information provided by you, information we collect when you visit our website, transaction information, and information we collect about you from third party sources. This information may include:

  * Social Security Number
  * Account Balances, Employment Information and Income
  * Credit History and Scores
  * Name
  * Physical Mailing Address, including Zip Code
  * Email Address
  * Telephone Number(s)
  * Mobile Number(s)
  * IP Address
  * Geo-Location Data

#### Why?

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law, along with some state laws, give consumers the right to limit some, but not all, sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand how we use your information.

#### How?

All financial companies need to share **Customer's** personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their **Customer's** personal information; the reasons **Speedy Cash** chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.

Reasons we can share your personal information | Does Speedy Cash share | Can you limit this sharing?  
---|---|---  
For our everyday business purposes \- such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus  | Yes | No  
For our marketing purposes \- to offer our products and services to you  | Yes | No  
For joint marketing with other financial companies | Yes | No  
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes \- information about your transactions and experiences  | Yes | No  
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes \- information about your creditworthiness  | Yes | Yes  
For our affiliates to market to you | Yes | Yes  
For nonaffiliates to market to you | Yes | Yes  
  
Click here to access our opt-out mail form.

Please note: If you are a **_new_** Customer, we can begin sharing your information **30** days from the date you complete your first transaction with us. When you are **_no longer_** our Customer, we continue to share your information as described in this policy; you can contact us at any time, however, to limit our sharing.

#### Who is providing this policy?

Speedy Cash group of companies which provides, or arranges, for consumers to obtain various financial products and services such as loans and check cashing.

#### How does Speedy Cash protect my personal information?

We take reasonable precautions to protect the personal information collected or maintained by us against loss, unauthorized access, and illegal use or disclosure. As examples, these measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings, among other things. We use encryption software to protect the security of individuals' personal information during transmission of such information through our websites (for example, the information provided by consumers when submitting an application to us for a loan product).

#### How does Speedy Cash collect my personal information?

We collect personal information on individuals only as allowed by law. We limit the collection of personal information to what is relevant and necessary to accomplish a lawful purpose.

We do not collect home, business or email addresses, or account information from persons who simply browse our internet website. The information we do automatically collect includes the domain name or Internet Protocol address that relates to the machine or device used to access our website, the type of browser and operating system used, the date and time when the website is visited, device ID if you are on a mobile device, and web pages displayed.

Like many websites, this site uses "session cookies" and "persistent cookie" technology. Persistent cookies are small text files that our website places within your browser so that it can remember you when you show up again later—like cookie crumbs. None of these cookies store any of your personal information. We use persistent cookies to enhance your experience on our website while also protecting your privacy, as well as enhancing the functionality and performance of our website, and for analytical purposes. On our website, temporary cookies, also called session cookies, may be placed within your browser and expire as soon as you exit our site. Typically, session cookies are used to facilitate interactions between you and the fields in forms on our website.

Managing cookie preferences differs from browser to browser, please refer to your web browser for further information. If you would like to disable cookies from SpeedyCash.com, please use the help function in your web browser to restrict cookies from our website.

We use Google Analytics to see how visitors are using SpeedyCash.com. Google Analytics reports traffic patterns anonymously. We may collect non-identifying information, such as the type of browser and browser version you are using to access our website, the day and time you access our website, the referring website that linked you directly to our website (if you arrived here by clicking a link on another website), and limited geographic information. **No personally identifiable information is collected for this purpose.**

Although we do not collect personally identifiable information on consumers that visit our website, there exists the possibility that other third parties conduct online tracking on our website and app over which we do not control.

You may link your Facebook account to your SpeedyCash.com account, which allows us to obtain information from your Facebook account (like your friends or contacts). The information we get from Facebook often depends on your settings and Facebook’s privacy policy. You have the ability to restrict the information we have access to by updating the settings within your Facebook account. In addition, you can also disconnect your Facebook account from your SpeedyCash.com account at any time. If you link your accounts, Speedy Cash will not market to any of your Facebook friends or contacts.

#### Online Tracking

We partner with companies that deliver ads for our financial products and services on sites that you visit on the web. In order to provide you with a more appropriate online experience, some of our ads that you may see are based on your previous online activity on our websites and other websites. Information about your online activities, combined with other information, may be used to select an ad for a product or service that better matches your interests - which is called online behavioral advertising (OBA) or interest-based advertising.

You can opt out from receiving ads based on your online behavior either by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) opt out page at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. If you elect to opt out of OBA, you will still see ads, but they may not be as pertinent to you. Please keep in mind that opting out is cookie-based and will only affect the specific computer and browser on which the opt-out cookie is applied. If you delete your browser cookies or if you use a different computer or a different browser and want to continue to be opted out of OBA, you will need to opt out again.

#### How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals

SpeedyCash.com does not currently have the capability to recognize the various Do Not Track signals or mechanisms from different web browsers. For more information on Do Not Track please visit <http://www.allaboutdnt.org/>.

#### CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

We only use or disclose personal information for the specified purposes, or purposes consistent with those purposes, unless we get the consent of the subject of the information, or unless required by law or regulation.

#### North Dakota Residents

We will not disclose information about your with non-affiliated, third party companies or financial institutions, other than as required or permitted by law, without your express permission.

#### Affiliates

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. Our affiliates include companies with a common ownership as Speedy Cash/Rapid Cash.

#### Nonaffiliates

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They may be financial and nonfinancial companies. Nonaffiliates include marketing companies which sell information for marketing purposes.

#### Joint marketing

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. Joint marketing partners include pre-paid card companies, partners that promote our products, and other lending companies.

Our Privacy Policy reflects our current business practices and is subject to change without notice.

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, add, revise or delete provisions of our Privacy Policy at any time. We will post the effective date of any change at the beginning of our Privacy Policy. We encourage you to visit our website regularly so that you remain aware of the terms and conditions and how our Privacy Policy may affect you.
